[
  {
    "question":
    {
      "prompt": "She ___ him about the train strike.",
      "optionA": "warned",
      "optionB": "complained",
      "optionC": "regretted",
      "rightOption": "a"
    }
  },
  {
    "question":
    {
      "prompt": "Helen ___ having lost my keys.",
      "optionA": "discussed",
      "optionB": "suggested",
      "optionC": "adimitted",
      "rightOption": "c"
    }
  },
  {
    "question":
    {
      "prompt": "The lawyer ___ that I should contact him.",
      "optionA": "offered",
      "optionB": "insisted",
      "optionC": "denied",
      "rightOption": "b"
    }
  },
  {
    "question":
    {
      "prompt": "My mother ___ to write the letter for me.",
      "optionA": "agreed",
      "optionB": "discussed",
      "optionC": "commented",
      "rightOption": "a"
    }
  },
  {
    "question":
    {
      "prompt": "Carla suggested ___ you.",
      "optionA": "that I text",
      "optionB": "I texting",
      "optionC": "me to text",
      "rightOption": "a"
    }
  },
  {
    "question":
    {
      "prompt": "Several people ___ on what good company she was.",
      "optionA": "warned",
      "optionB": "recommended",
      "optionC": "agreed",
      "rightOption": "c"
    }
  },
  {
    "question":
    {
      "prompt": "Emily ___ for being late",
      "optionA": "confessed",
      "optionB": "accused",
      "optionC": "apologized",
      "rightOption": "c"
    }
  },
  {
    "question":
    {
      "prompt": "Stella ___ us to meet her at the museum.",
      "optionA": "reminded",
      "optionB": "insisted",
      "optionC": "suggested",
      "rightOption": "a"
    }
  },
  {
    "question":
    {
      "prompt": "Jake ___ giving up his studies.",
      "optionA": "regretted",
      "optionB": "blamed",
      "optionC": "congratulated",
      "rightOption": "a"
    }
  },
  {
    "question":
    {
      "prompt": "They ___ me for losing the match.",
      "optionA": "told",
      "optionB": "blamed",
      "optionC": "advise",
      "rightOption": "b"
    }
  },
  {
    "question":
    {
      "prompt": "She ___ me to start studying Spanish.",
      "optionA": "encouraged",
      "optionB": "admitted",
      "optionC": "insisted",
      "rightOption": "a"
    }
  },
  {
    "question":
    {
      "prompt": "My friends congratulated ___.",
      "optionA": "me on my new car",
      "optionB": "on my new car",
      "optionC": "my new car",
      "rightOption": "a"
    }
  },
  {
    "question":
    {
      "prompt": "My dad denied ___ those horrible curtains?",
      "optionA": "to buy",
      "optionB": "buy",
      "optionC": "buying",
      "rightOption": "c"
    }
  },
  {
    "question":
    {
      "prompt": "Paul insisted ___ for dinner.",
      "optionA": "to paying",
      "optionB": "paying",
      "optionC": "on paying",
      "rightOption": "c"
    }
  },
  {
    "question":
    {
      "prompt": "My mom ___ her old car.",
      "optionA": "offered me",
      "optionB": "offered",
      "optionC": "to offer",
      "rightOption": "a"
    }
  },
  {
    "question":
    {
      "prompt": "Mary ___ some chairs.",
      "optionA": "asked me to pick up",
      "optionB": "asked picking up",
      "optionC": "asked I pick up",
      "rightOption": "a"
    }
  },
  {
    "question":
    {
      "prompt": "He ___ this song.",
      "optionA": "said he liked",
      "optionB": "told he like",
      "optionC": "said liking",
      "rightOption": "a"
    }
  },
  {
    "question":
    {
      "prompt": "She ___ Italian.",
      "optionA": "confessed not to speak",
      "optionB": "confessed she didn't speak",
      "optionC": "confessed she didn't speaking",
      "rightOption": "b"
    }
  },
  {
    "question":
    {
      "prompt": "She told the boys ___ on the grass",
      "optionA": "not to play",
      "optionB": "don't play",
      "optionC": "not play",
      "rightOption": "a"
    }
  },
  {
    "question":
    {
      "prompt": "She _____ a job.",
      "optionA": "told to find",
      "optionB": "said me to find",
      "optionC": "told me to find",
      "rightOption": "c"
    }
  }
]
